<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.jf.goeditor.feature"
      label="org.jf.goeditor.feature"
      version="1.3.4">

   <description url="http://www.example.com/description">
      This little plugin helps you to browse resources with the &apos;Explorer&apos; of your platform
and Open selected file with your prefered editor(customable)
and Open shell in current selected file path.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      Copyright (c) 1999-2006 Emmanuel Boudrant, Cross Systems, nexB Inc.
 All rights reserved.
 Copyright (c) 2010-2014 纪秀峰  All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      /*
 * ====================================================================
 * The Apache Software License, Version 2.0
 *
 * Copyright (c) 1999-2006 Emmanuel Boudrant, Cross Systems, nexB Inc.
 * All rights reserved.
 * Copyright (c) 2010-2014 纪秀峰  All rights reserved.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
 * modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
 * are met:
 *
 * 1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
 *    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
 *
 * 2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
 *    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
 *    the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
 *    distribution.
 *
 * 3. The end-user documentation included with the redistribution, if
 *    any, must include the following acknowlegement:
 *       &quot;This product includes software developed by the
 *        EasyStruts project team (http://easystruts.sf.net).&quot;
 *    Alternately, this acknowlegement may appear in the software itself,
 *    if and wherever such third-party acknowlegements normally appear.
 *
 * 4. The names &quot;EsayStruts&quot;, &quot;EasyExplore&quot;, &quot;nexB&quot;, &quot;Struts&quot;, and
 *    &quot;EasyEclipse&quot; must not be used to endorse or promote products derived
 *    from this software without prior written permission. For written
 *    permission, please contact info@nexb.com.
 *
 * 5. Products derived from this software may not be called &quot;EasyStruts&quot;
 *    nor may &quot;EasyStruts&quot; appear in their names without prior written
 *    permission of the EasyStruts project team.
 *
 * THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED
 * WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES
 * OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
 * DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE APACHE SOFTWARE FOUNDATION OR
 * ITS CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
 * SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
 * LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF
 * USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND
 * ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY,
 * OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT
 * OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
 * SUCH DAMAGE.
 * ====================================================================
 */
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="goto_editor" url="http://emacs-java.github.io/eclipse_goto_editor/update-site/"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="org.jf.goeditor"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
